{
  "topic_id":"102",
  "questions": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "question": "Which of the following sentences is correctly punctuated?",
      "choice": [
        "Everyone has special skills some people use them very well.",
        "Everyone has special skills; some people use them very well.",
        "Everyone has special skills and, some people use them very well.",
        "Everyone has special skills; and, some people use them very well."
      ],
      "answer": 1,
      "explanation": "",
      "keywords": []
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "question": "What is the best way to punctuate the following sentence?",
      "choice": [
        "The class was comprised of thirty.two students.",
        "The class was comprised of thirty/two students.",
        "The class was comprised (of thirty_two students).",
        "The class was comprised of thirty-two students."
      ],
      "answer": 3,
      "explanation": "",
      "keywords": []
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "question": "Which of the following sentences are punctuated and capitalized correctly?",
      "choice": [
        "For the good of us all please think before you act next time!",
        "For the good of us all, please think before you act next time.",
        "for the good of us all, please think before you act next time.",
        "For the good of us all please think before you act next time"
      ],
      "answer": 1,
      "explanation": "",
      "keywords": []
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "question": "Which sentence is punctuated correctly?",
      "choice": [
        "I yelped, 'That hurts.'",
        "I yelped, 'That hurts.'.",
        "I yelped, 'That hurts!'",
        "I yelped, 'That hurts!'."
      ],
      "answer": 2,
      "explanation": "",
      "keywords": []
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "question": "Which sentence is punctuated correctly?",
      "choice": [
        "Edwin said, that he was fine.",
        "Edwin said 'that he was fine.'",
        "Edwin said that he was fine.",
        "Edwin said, 'that he was fine.'"
      ],
      "answer": 2,
      "explanation": "",
      "keywords": []
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "question": "Choose the sentence with the correct punctuation.",
      "choice": [
        "You are my best friend, Kaylin.",
        "You, are my best friend, Kaylin.",
        "You are my best friend Kaylin.",
        "You are my, best, friend, Kaylin."
      ],
      "answer": 0,
      "explanation": "",
      "keywords": []
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "question": "Which sentence is punctuated correctly?",
      "choice": [
        "Carlos said, 'that he was starving.'",
        "Carlos said 'that he was starving.'",
        "Carlos said that he was starving.",
        "Carlos said, that he was starving."
      ],
      "answer": 2,
      "explanation": "",
      "keywords": []
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
      "question": "Which of the following sentences is punctuated correctly?",
      "choice": [
        "Mrs. Duarte is our English teacher.",
        "Mrs Duarte is our English teacher.",
        "Mrs. Duarte is our English teacher?",
        "Mrs Duarte is our English teacher?"
      ],
      "answer": 0,
      "explanation": "",
      "keywords": []
    },
    {
      "id": 9,
      "question": "Which of the following sentences is punctuated correctly?",
      "choice": [
        "'Watch out' Ricardo hollered.",
        "'Watch out!' Ricardo hollered.",
        "'Watch out! Ricardo hollered.",
        "Watch out!Ricardo hollered."
      ],
      "answer": 0,
      "explanation": "",
      "keywords": []
    },
    {
      "id": 10,
      "question": "Which of the following sentences is punctuated correctly?",
      "choice": [
        "Sadly, I walked home.",
        "Sadly I walked home.",
        "Sadly I walked, home.",
        "Sadly, I walked, home."
      ],
      "answer": 0,
      "explanation": "",
      "keywords": []
    }
  ]
}
